



# **Azadeh Ahmadi**

**Date of birth :**(29/10/2001) | **Nationality:**Afghan | **Gender:** Female |

| Email address: azadehahmadi223@gmail.com | WhatsApp Messanger: (+93 728039939) |

Address: Afghanistan, Herat City-District4

#### About me:

I am a Full-Stack Developer with 3 years experience in user interface design, Website development, programming, and solution implementation. Certified in Both front-end and back-end technologies. Self-independent, reliable and friendly Individual who works hard to achieve his goals.

Adaptable quickly, and organized well. Interested in learning the latest web & software technologies quickly. Able to work well in teams as well as individually. My future goal is to become a senior full-stack developer.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2022 - PRESENT - CTI, AFghanistan

#### FULLSTACK WEB-DEVELOPER -CTI

2017 - Oloom - e - Maaser , Afghanistan

### ENGLISG LANGUAGE CERTIFICATE - Oloom- e - Maaser

2018 - Oloom- e - Maaser, Afghanistan

#### **ENGLISG LANGUAGE DIPLOMA** – Oloom– e – Maaser

2017 - ARCS, Afghanistan

## **HEALT FIRST AID CERTIFICATE – ARCS**

2024 - CTI, Afghanistan

# FRONT-END WEB-DEVELOPER CERTIFICATE - CTI

2019 - Imam-Shush-Noor High School, Afghanistan

## SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE – Imamm-Shesh-Noor High School

2020 - OPD Ahmad Jami Clinic, AFghanistan

# Nurse CERTIFICATE- OPD Ahmad Jami Clinic

### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/01/2022 - PRESENT, AFghanistan

### **FULL-STACK WEB-DEVELOPER –** Freelancer

Some of my projects as a Full-Stack Web-Developer that created, designed and developed.

- Dots Menu Animation(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Number Gussing Game(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Personal Portfolio(Html5, Tailwind.css, Js, React).
- Pig Game(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Model Window(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Personal Portfolio(Html5, BootStrap, Js, React).
- Color Game(Html5, Css3, JQuery).
- Food Recepi(Html5, Css3, Js, React).
- Color Game(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Personal Portfolio(Html5, Css3, Js, React).
- Add Card Form(React, Css3).
- Afghan Explore Province(Html5, Css3, Js, React).
- Fashion-Focus(Html5, Css3, Js, React).
- Personal Portfolio(Html5, Css3, Js, React).
- Magic Login Form(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Desig-Your-House(Html5, Css3, Js).

- Login and Register Website(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Sidebar Tuturial Design(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Card-Hover-Effect Design(Html5, Css3, Js).
- Create Project Website(Html5, Tailwind.css, Js, React).
- Capstone Project-Blog App With image uploads(Html5, Css3, Js, NodeJs, Express, Ejs)

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

### **VOLUNTEERING**

**English Language Teacher:** I worked voluntarily as a teacher at Hoomay Saadat Private School.

Computer Teacher: I worked voluntarily as a teacher at Mergan Training Course.

Work as a Nurse: I worked as a Nurse at OPD Ahmad Jami Clinic.

ARCS: I worked in Afghanistan Red Crescent Society (ARCS) Since (2016-present).

Rasa Production: I worked in Rasa Production Two years (2020–2022).

# Imam Javad Charity Organization-2 year.

• I was responsible for updating the website, managing content, and supporting the development of donation and campaign features. I also played and active role in managing the foundation's social media, creating effective post, analyzing audience feedback, and promoting charity campaigns through digital tools.

### As a Teacher Duty

# 1. Monthly Plan:

- Having an exam
- Giving a gift for best student
- Having meeting with parents

# 2. Weekly Plan:

• Checking the attendance sheet and report for office

# 3. Daily Plan:

- Coming on time on class
- Having good timing with students
- Having the attendance sheet
- Solving their problem
- Checking the homework
- And answering for their question
- And giving their new lesson

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):Persion

Other language(s):				
	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING	WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Speakin	g Writing
ENGLISH	Excellent		Mediume	Perfect
Pashto	Excellent	Perfect	Good	Excellent

### FRON-END SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | TawilandCss | React | VueJs | Figma | UI/UX | JQuery | Web & App design

### **BACK-END SKILLS**

Nodejs | Express | Phython | Json | SQL | Git | | Github |

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Microsoft Office | Typography | Photoshop | Illustrator | Indesign | Image & Video Editing | Coding | Branding | AfterEffects | Web & App design | Wireframe, Mockup, Prototype |

### HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Coding | Photography | Play Football | Book club | painting | Lisining Poudcast | Teach Online | Yoga | Self Development | Watching Tutorials

### COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Collaboration | Effective Verbal Communication | Active Listening | Empathy | Adaptability | Constructive Feedback | Confidence | Conflict Resolution | Able to adjust in different environment

#### MANAGEMENT AND LEADERSHIP SKILLS

Organizing | Classroom Management | Decision Making | Mentoring and Coaching | Curriculum Development | Teamwork & Time management |

#### RECOMMANDATIONS

Safiullah Fetrat (Head of Chemistry department at Herat University)

Phone: (0796100076)

Email: fetrat457472@yahoo.com

• Somaya Ahmadi (Graphic Designer in Code To Inspire)

Phone: (0748588456)

Email: somayaahmadi644@gmail.com